What are the most challenging economics
of the magazine industry?
Was the goal to reinvent
the business model?
Certainly that's the goal.
I think, you know,
most small independent
magazine businesses are folding
because they're not
thinking outside the box.
Time is of the essence.
There's so much going on.
How can you fight for people's attention?
What can we make that will actually break
through and matter?
Karlie Kloss is many things,
but let's start with supermodel.
Karlie!
A businesswoman.
I invest in companies and
ideas and people I believe in.
Money is power.
And she's in the headlines
whether she wants them or not.
You and Josh are very private
people. Is that intentional?
It is because we really
care about our real life.
I think nobody else
deserves access to that.
Did it change when
President Trump was elected? No.
Long before that as a model
I think it was definitely
a line I had to walk.
Now in her biggest bet yet
she's going from covergirl
to medium mogul, buying
up iconic magazines
as the industry fights
to survive in a world
dominated by digital media.
I think about it like
we're running a startup
inside a vintage car.
So how does a woman who's
graced over a hundred covers
aim to reinvent this treasured
but struggling format
and keep reinventing herself?
So what kind of kid were you? Were you the
wallflower or the bookworm?
The queen bee? I was a
total nerd.
Obviously we need your yearbook.
I need to meet your
teachers, your prom date.
To find out, we're entering her world.
A life built in New York City
that all began in the Midwest.
You are on the cover of all of these.
Oh, and the, there's many,
many more, but we've don't have time.
So this is your
high school.
This is Webster Groves High School.
I imagine this brings back memories.
Oh, so many memories.
You're a nineties baby. You're down here.
I mean hopefully.
Although I think I was in China
doing a photo shoot on the
Great Wall for Vogue.
As one does.
I would be in here.
So you were on the Great Wall
of China while everyone
else was in the gym.
Yes. Taking a photo. But
that's also just such a perfect example of
how you held these two worlds.
Oh it was my life. I
wouldn't want it any other way.
Kloss's modeling career
happened basically overnight,
but back in high school she
was a self-proclaimed nerdy
teenager just trying
to get a date to prom.
Is it true that you
rejected her? Oh well you
rejected is
a
strong word.
Karlie is that
how you would put it?
That is how I would.
You did end up going
to prom together senior year.
Yes we did. And you did end
up wearing Dior. I saw that.
I did end up wearing Dior
Couture. So you, box checked.
It was beautiful and it was
orange and I got my tuxedo from
Men's Warehouse.
Hello. My
parents'
home.
Welcome. Thank you to your mom
and dad I should say, for having us here.
What was the biggest
culture shock when you went
into the modeling world?
I think I just was always
authentically who I am,
which is a girl from the Midwest
until I was 13 years old.
I never flew on an
airplane, like my family
and I drove cross-country
for family vacations.
So fast forward to when I'm 15 years old
and I have a Cinderella story,
truly overnight success.
I walk in the Calvin Klein
New York Fashion Week show
and it just puts me on the
map in such a crazy way.
And so quite quickly at 15
I was jet setting between,
you know the suburbs of St.
Louis and Paris, Tokyo, New York.
Oh wow. They cut a circle into square
slices.
You didn't know math would allow
it. Here we are, mom, come.
Okay. Hi mom. I'm introducing
her to Emo's Pizza.
As a mom, like what was it like
for you sending your daughter off
to the runway when she was a teenager?
It was exciting.
It was such a learning experience
and the world became your classroom.
I imagine you made a
lot of money very fast.
How did you deal with that?
I started working so young
and was so fortunate
to sort of make income
that I could have never dreamt of
and it really happened
around the same time
of the '08 crisis
and my family was really impacted
as many families in this country were,
and we went through bankruptcy
and we lost, you know,
the roof over our head
and it was like, it was an
incredibly painful period.
I also was beginning my career
and was able to support my family,
support my sisters through school.
And so for me my career
was a, a way to be able
to like support the
people I cared most about.
My mom saved like newspaper clippings
and all the things
through all the years. You
are on the cover of all of these.
Oh, and there's many, many
more, but we don't have time.
That doesn't to
me even look like you.
It doesn't even look
like me, right?
No. Can I tell you that's
what being a great model is,
is that you, you transform.
I started modeling at a period
where like you were seen
and not heard to then
the dawn of social media
where you can speak your truth,
you can build your name into a brand,
and models became celebrities.
It started to become Karlie
and what she has to say, what she's doing,
what she stands for.
Yeah. Hi guys, I'm Karlie Kloss
and welcome to my YouTube channel.
With social media,
suddenly Kloss had a
platform beyond the runway.
It's New York Fashion Week
and I'm on my way to Michael Kors.
She launched
her own YouTube channel at the
dawn of the creator economy.
I'm in love. It's perfect.
Started her first
business, Karlie's Kookies,
which funded over half a
million school lunches.
Took a life-changing coding
course at the Flatiron School
and in 2019 stepped into
Heidi Klum's iconic role as host
of Project Runway.
Off Camera. Kloss was making bets on
where culture was moving, backing a range
of budding startups.
What I do with my capital
is I invest in companies
and ideas and people I believe in.
I support issues that I care deeply about,
like money is power.
Was there a moment
where you decided I don't
wanna be a model forever
and that you wanted to have
a career beyond modeling?
Yeah, I think since I started
this career I've always been
thinking about what comes after.
For a long time, I thought
of it as a means to an end
to be able to make money and
then also to see the world
and not only that, being the ateliers
of the most brilliant
creatives in the industry.
I love walking runways.
You don't turn that off.
It's a part of who I am,
but I think it's never
been all of who I am.
You've bought Life Magazine,
you bought the fashion
magazine i-D from Vice.
You led a group of
investors to buy W Magazine.
What's the grand vision for Bedford Media?
Bedford is sort of taking
this startup approach
to these sort of heritage brands.
I mean, Life is 90 years old.
I think about it like
we're running a startup
inside a vintage car.
Independent small media
should continue to exist.
I have an incredible
editor-in-chief at i-D
and the editorial team
and the commercial team.
My role is more like helping protect and
and grow the business.
I just want to help, you
know, build better businesses
around these brands.
A business model that everyone seems
to think is dying, right?
For sure. I've said like
I feel like I'm the person
running into a burning building.
I mean here's i-D,
I mean you own this
magazine now, can we just..
Not just this one for $12.99.
No, I'm so proud of the fact
that I am continuing this legacy
Today,
Kloss is taking us to
New York City for a look
behind the cover of Bedford
Media, the company she founded
with her husband Josh Kushner.
Bedford is built on a simple idea.
Legacy magazines with decades
of cultural credibility are worth saving
Love a New York Street.
Oh, this is a real one.
What magazines were you reading as a kid?
I, I don't think I was reading
magazines until I was in them.
I mean you were thirteen
when you started?
So I guess yeah,
but I, you know for me
like magazines are the
platform to tell stories.
Yeah, to show ideas, to
showcase people. Yeah.
It's not just to sort of
continue to chug along something
that I'm nostalgic about,
but actually we consume more stories
and information than ever.
I was thinking a lot about the Life photo
archive, which is iconic.
I mean space and
Oh. War. I mean American history,
civil rights, right?
Like there's some photos
of you in there. Yes.
What are the possibilities there?
The archive is incredible.
Life was really the platform
that showed what was happening
around the world before we
lived in such a globally
connected, digitally immersive world.
And so a photograph told a
whole story about a person,
about a war, about what was happening
that you might not see in your day to day.
And I think that to me like
that resonates so much.
I mean it's such a privilege
to, to take a brand like that
and to think about how to
bring it to life today.
What is Life moving forward?
Well, Life Magazine,
you'll have to wait and see.
While the future of life
is still taking shape.
i-D Magazine is up
and running in the heart
of the Lower East Side.
There's a lot of things that
are in the works right now.
We just launched our spring
issue. Fashion month madness just
happened and they like covered it all.
Come meet everybody. Yeah.
Hi
This is Emily.
Thanks for having us.
Wait, I love these mics though. These
are, who runs around with
these kind of? All of us.
Yeah.
Is this like man or
woman on the street kind
of a thing? Like this is,
Yeah.
Hi i-D, hi i-D, hi i-D.
Hi i-d, I'm Sarah and
I'm at the Prada show.
Hi i-D, my name is Bhavitha Mandava.
We cover it all.
Yes, I love it. It's
true, the
pulse. What is i-D's point of view?
Trish and Terry Jones founded
i-D. Terry Jones literally
hand stapled the magazines himself
and he invented something
called the Straight Up,
which is the modern day sort
of street style photography.
The media landscape has totally changed.
There's digital, there's print,
there's experiential, there's merch.
What's the overall strategy?
I think like to continue
to innovate within all
of these spaces and reach
people where they are.
I don't think that we're gonna
have like Facebook outcomes
on this investment necessarily,
but like that's not my intention here.
Like my intention is to build
a really viable business
but to make really meaningful
work along the way.
Maybe you're not looking
for Facebook outcomes,
but like what do you see
as the real business
opportunity in an industry
that has very challenging economics?
When we bought this business
out of bankruptcy, we had
to fully rebuild all pieces of it.
The commercial business,
the creative agency piece,
the editorial team. The last
two years have been sort
of rebuilding the core business
and that really has
been part of this thesis
with Bedford is like how can we build
and run our website without
a hundred person tech team?
Like how can we run
and build, you know, all parts
of the business in a leaner,
scrappier, startup way?
And that candidly is part of
the advantage we have to a lot
of the other sort of industry
because there's a lot of people
like having to lay off a lot
of parts of these businesses
because the business model
can't sustain it anymore.
Who do you see as your
closest competition right now?
We are our own competition.
I'm not overly commercial
about this either.
Like I don't want to squeeze it to a point
that it actually loses its soul.
Like that would also not be success to me.
We're seeing the world's
biggest billionaires also
getting into media.
Mark Benioff with Time.
Jeff Bezos with the Washington
Post, Elon Musk with X.
There's a lot of anxiety
about editorial independence.
Who do you think is doing it right
and what worries you the most?
To me like
that's been very clear from
the start is like our editorial
team has editorial independence.
I think it's like, the
intention, you know,
for me really comes from like
how can I support this artist colony?
And not just in a philanthropic way,
but like actually how
can I push it to grow
and keep getting, you know,
smarter with the times
Curating i-D's
soul with Kloss is Steff Yotka
i-D's global editorial director.
She's tasked with keeping
the magazine on the cutting
edge of youth culture.
What is Karlie's role day to
day like? How involved is she?
Every other job I've had,
the person in her role
is like a old white guy.
And so it's great to be able
to have these conversations
about the present
and the future of i-D with
someone who isn't like stymied
by a conservative view
of what media should be.
Everyone has content
everywhere at their fingertips.
Why do we need magazines?
Because we love them. We could
have just made an Instagram
or we could have just made a TikTok,
but I think the reason to
have a print magazine is
that it does mean it's forever.
It will never be deleted
from the internet.
It is a physical object that is a record
of what we thought was cool.
Kloss isn't just trying to disrupt media,
she's also trying to expand
who gets a seat at the table in
tech?
Apply to Kode with Klossy.
In 2015 she launched Kode with
Klossy, a free coding camp
for girls because who's
in the room matters. I am
one.
What do you think is the value
of reaching girls at that age?
Like 13 to 18? Yeah. Which
is the Kode with Klossy age.
Yeah. There's so many studies
around why girls self-select out in math
and decide that they're not good at math
or STEM topics broadly
long before 13 years old.
We are creating a space
to come participate in
like the creative applications of code.
Especially girls that are not given access
to these tools or they
don't think it's for them.
I'm so proud of our
12,000 alum, just over 70%
of them who go into college major
or minor in computer science.
What I care about is that
there are girls and women
and people of all sorts of
lived experience helping inform
that technology at all levels.
Josh guess.
Hi, how are you? Thanks for
sharing her with us today.
That's Josh Kushner,
Kloss's husband, founder
of Thrive Capital, a venture firm
that's backed Spotify,
Skims, A24, Instagram
and is making a major bet on OpenAI.
You and Josh have been
together since you were 19,
I believe when you met you
were a lot more famous.
I always like to tease him.
I was a lot more successful
than he was when we first met.
You decided to convert to Judaism.
Did you have any Kristen Bell?
Nobody Wants This moments.
Who the hell is that?
It's not us. It's not? No.
Oh my gosh. My friend's
actually the writer
of the show and I texted her.
I was like, girl, for season 2, 3, 4,
I got more material for you.
Like call me. You know? I
fell in love with somebody,
his faith was a huge part of who he is
and I knew that from the start
and choosing that I wanted it in my life.
I'm really proud of that choice.
As Kloss's personal life
played out publicly,
it drew no shortage of opinions,
Not even to dinner with the Kushner's?
Oh, that's your husband.
You're married to a man
whose brother happens
to be married to Ivanka Trump.
How do you deal with everything
that comes with that?
Well, I know who I am.
I know the values that guide my life
and the issues that I care about.
So, you know, I haven't
lost sight of who I am,
but also it's, it's my husband's family.
What's conversation
like at family dinners?
Well, we're sitting here in St. Louis,
which is a blue dot in a red state.
Since as long as I can remember
I've always been exposed
to a lot of different
political points of view
and I think that trained me for my life.
You know, I'm a Democrat.
I think it's possible
to have relationships with people
who you politically don't align with.
And I think this country
has always been a place
for, for dialogue.
We have to be able to talk to each other.
Have you had any conversations
with President Trump about politics?
I have never met President Trump.
We're trying to, to give
Emily a taste of the best
of St. Louis here. We're, we're
eating a lot.
We're eating our way through,
but I'll call you back.
Alright. And let you, I'll speak to you
later. Okay. Love you. Bye.
You've used your voice to platform causes
that you believe in.
You are very active
around abortion rights,
protecting access to clinics.
You've been a Planned Parenthood escort.
People are traveling hundreds,
if not thousands of miles
to seek access to basic and
lifesaving reproductive care.
And especially, you know,
in a place like Missouri,
you know, it's the first state.
Six minutes after Roe v. Wade was
overturned, it had a trigger law
that went into effect.
Where are you doubling down right now?
I've been here many times over
the past few years helping
fight for the ballot initiative.
And we passed the ballot
initiative for access
to reproductive rights here
in the state of Missouri.
We're going to have to
continue to protect it.
This should not be
political in my perspective.
So I started Gateway Coalition,
which we've helped move
more than $4 million
to little clinics across the country
that are holding up access to care.
I feel like it would be so easy
for someone in your position
to not say anything,
but you really are using your voice.
You're speaking up, you're
speaking almost louder.
Do you feel like a pressure
that you didn't necessarily ask for?
Listen, that's life.
I made the choice a long time
ago to one, be with the person
that I love despite any
complications that came with it.
Two, not to lose sight of who I am in that
and three, to just
continue to stand up for
and fight for the things
that I care about.
Karlie Kloss has spent her
life proving some things just
don't have to be mutually exclusive
and her hometown is all
in, where there's a street
and even frozen custard to back it up.
This is a big deal. Hi.
Hi. Do you still have a flavor
named after Karlie Kloss?
We do. The Karlie crete.
Is it still an action?
Stop. It's, it's our
chip and the
granola.
I'm gonna have Karlie crete.
Make it two.
How does one get a flavor
named after them at a,
I honestly had nothing to do with it.
It's the greatest
accomplishment of my entire life
outside of my children.
For real.
Still rolling?
Yes. We're still rolling.
Okay. That's why we call
a concrete. Oh my gosh.
Thank you Josh. We have
to do it. Okay. Ready?
Ready. Oh my gosh.
There we go. The finest
of St. Louis everyone.
You accomplished so much in
such a short amount of time.
Like what is the next chapter?
I feel very grateful
that I started so young
because I have lived so
much and I'm 33 years old
and I have three young
children under five years old.
I, I've worked so hard so
that I can enjoy this moment in my life
and be so present with them.
Doesn't mean I'm like working any less,
but I'm just hyper conscious
of like wanting to enjoy this
moment.
Yeah, well here's to enjoying
in this chapter. Amen.
of your life and eating
lots of ice cream. Mm
Cheers.
Perfect.
So I wanted you to put your
Project Runway hat on. Okay.
Along with your tech hat.
I just wanna get a few like
style reviews.
Okay. Yes. Give it to me.
I mean iconic, what can we say? Steve
Jobs like invented the black turtleneck.
Okay. This is more of an evolution.
Mm Oh yes. I think he's come a long way.
He's living his best life
and expressing that through fashion.
Like good for you. Yeah.
I love that. In or out.
Was it ever in? Yes.
By the way, I think
this is a Schiaparelli set.
Or maybe it was Tom Brown. Very stylish.
It looks like he was wearing
the vest in the early days.
Well you know, you are cold
but you wanna have your sleeves out.
Palmer Luckey. To
each their own.
right.
And that is the beauty of fashion. Yeah.
Jensen just like is what a legend. Truly.
And like a style icon.
Like those leather jackets.
Man, Josh is that way.
Josh wears the same
thing every single day.
Since you mentioned it.
Yes. My sweet husband,
he's got a great sweater collection.
This is probably his.